<Document>
  #ZERO TOLERANCE RULES

  You may be banned for violating any of the rules below with little to no warning.



  ##Don't harass or target players across rounds.

  - Absolutely no hate speech, slurs, bigotry, racism, sexism, ableism, or any other form of real world discrimination. This includes using letter substitutions to disguise offensive language or as a "joke".

  - Speciesism is allowed so long as it is not used as a stand-in for real bigotry/hate.



  ##No sexual act should ever be done or mentioned.

  - Genitalia should never be given explicit description.

  - Distasteful but non-sexual bravado do not apply to this so long as it is not directed towards another player.

  - Euphemisms that also have a sexual meaning are allowed in non-sexual contexts. Common terms or phrases like “Suck my dick”, "Go fuck yourself", etc are fine, as long as saying such is not a literal invitation or solicitation to do so.



  ##This is not a dating server.

  - Romantic relationships depicted in-game (marriage, dating, etc) between characters are not allowed.

  - We have underage players here, this is not the place to find your husband/wife.



  ##Players need to be the age of 13 or above.

  - This rule is for the benefit of and is meant to protect people who shouldn't be playing here due to the nature of the SS14 community.

  - Those who are not showing the maturity associated with being of this age will be banned.



  ##Use of VPNs/Proxies.

  - You may not use a VPN or proxy.

  - If you have a special reason for using a VPN (such as censorship from your country), you may request special permission from one of the hosts via the Discord.



  ##Don't use multiple SS14 accounts to play.

  - Players knowingly using multiple SS14 accounts will have all of their accounts banned. Appeal with the account you intend to use.

  - Players should avoid sharing accounts. Any actions taken on a shared account will be noted for the use of the account, and not per player using it.

  - If you wish to switch accounts or loose access to your SS14 account you must ahelp ingame with both accounts to transfer your notes and bans. Game Admins reserve the right to request more information or contact through discord or the forums to confirm it is indeed your account.



  ##Don't harass or target players across rounds.

  - Annoying players for in character reasons in the current round is fine; having a multi-round character dispute requires their permission.

  - Do not annoy or target players out of character for actions they took in any round.

  - Do not threaten or imply to players that you are calling the admins on them.

  - Do not harass players between rounds or out of game for playing a specific role or character.

  - Do not annoy or target players for not using the 'meta' or winning strategy.

  - Do not share personally identifying or sensitive information about others.

  - Do not discuss, complain, or comment about anyone's admin bans/notes/actions including your own through OOC channels or otherwise. If you've been banned or disagree with an action, the person involved must make an appeal. We do allow discussing bans in our discord for transparency reasons so long as it remains a civil discussion.



  ##Do not harass or slander other servers.

  - Per the hub rules of SS14, do not speak negatively of other SS14 servers (including their staff and community) in an uncivil or slanderous manner.

  - We value free speech and opinion, but will take action if you violate hub rules and/or raid/harass other servers.



  ##Don't exploit.

  - Don't use exploits of bugs or external programs to gain an advantage, or disrupt the server in any way.

  - Using an external program to calculate coordinate locations is permitted.

  - Using an external program for accessibility purposes is permitted so long as it provides no major advantage to the player.



  ##Don't break the law.

  - CMU will permanently ban any individual without warning who engages in egregious criminal acts, whether on or off our server and will report such actions to the appropriate authorities.
</Document>
